Guide to the Susie Bright papers and On Our Backs records, 1978-2013.
Bright, Susie papers and On Our Backs records
- Series III. Writings
  - Media Books
    - Whole Earth: "Susie Bright and All Her Works", 1994 (Box 18, Folder 265)
    - Penthouse: "Is Sex Sexy Without Power?", 1995 (Box 18, Folder 266)
    - Elle (Italy): "Pasionaria del sesso", 1995 (Box 18, Folder 267)
    - New York Times: "You Can Be in Fashion, In the Light, or in the Pool", February 5, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 268)
    - San Jose Mercury News: "A Close-Up View of Sex-From the Other Side of the Bed", March 24, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 269)
    - Williams Free Press, April 10, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 270)
    - The Williams Record: "Susie Bright Delivers Sexual State of the Union", April 11, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 271)
    - "Erotique" Reviews, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 272)
    - Entertainment Weekly: "New Releases", May 19, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 273)
    - LA Weekly: "Let My People Come", May 12-18, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 274)
    - City on the Hill Press: "UCSC Graduate to Address the Sexual State of the Union", May 11, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 275)
    - Reviews of "Sexwise", 1995 (Box 18, Folder 276)
    - Santa Cruz Sentinel: "The X-rated Intellectual", June 11, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 277)
    - The Boston Phoenix: "America in the Age of Paradox", June 2, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 278)
    - New Woman: "Fast Read", June 1995 (Box 18, Folder 279)
    - Celluloid Closet Reviews, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 280)
    - "Erotique" Reviews, July 1995 (Box 18, Folder 281)
    - San Francisco Review of Books: "Susie Bright's Sexwise", July 16, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 282)
    - Playboy Forum: "Higher Ground", August 1995 (Box 18, Folder 283)
    - German articles about Susie Bright, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 284)
    - Impact: "An Interview of Sexpert Susie Bright", September 1995 (Box 18, Folder 285)
    - Playboy: "Lesbian Chic", September 1995 (Box 18, Folder 286)
    - Pulp: "Stuff We Red", 1995 (Box 18, Folder 287)
    - Publishers Weekly: "The Best American Erotica 1995", August 21, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 288)
    - SF Weekly: "I Spit on Your Dogma", August 2-8, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 289)
    - Elle, August 1995 (Box 18, Folder 290)
    - The Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review: "A Primer on Erotic Prose", 1995 (Box 18, Folder 291)
    - Diva: "Too Sexy for Her Shirt", December 1995-January 1996 (Box 18, Folder 292)
    - Magical Blend: "Jimi Hendrix and Why the Little Dykes Understand", January 1996 (Box 18, Folder 293)
    - Esquire: "Some Like 'Em Real", January 1996 (Box 18, Folder 294)
    - Shout: "Sex Sells: a Bookseller's Adventure", February 1996 (Box 18, Folder 295)
    - Curve: "Nothing But the Girl", February 1996 (Box 18, Folder 296)
    - Esquire: "Howard Stern, Your Book is In", March 1996 (Box 18, Folder 297)
    - The New Yorker: "The Movies", March 18, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 298)
    - Time: "The Final Frontier", March 11, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 299)
    - Movieline: "Out and On Screen", April 1996 (Box 18, Folder 300)
    - Premiere: "The Celluloid Closet", April 1996 (Box 18, Folder 301)
    - Playboy: "F.Y.I.: The Forum Bookshelf", April 1996 (Box 18, Folder 302)
    - F Newsmagazine: "Sex Talk", April 1996 (Box 18, Folder 303)
    - Playboy: "Pornography: Does it Suck?", May 1996 (Box 18, Folder 304)
    - Bound Reviews, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 305)
    - Esquire: "My Favorite Thing", June 1996 (Box 18, Folder 306)
    - Missouli Independent: "Susie Bright and the Politics of Porn", June 6-12, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 307)
    - Iowa City Independent: "Nothing but the Girl", June 15, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 308)
    - Reviews of "Nothing but the Girl", 1996 (Box 18, Folder 309)
    - Feminist Bookstore News: "Art Books", July-August 1996 (Box 18, Folder 310)
    - Gay Chicago News: "New Picture Books for Girls and Boys", August 1-11, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 311)
    - MSRRT: "Recommended Reading", July-August 1996 (Box 18, Folder 312)
    - Daily Mail: "Why We Should All Look Back in Anger", July 27, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 313)
    - London Times, July 26, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 314)
    - Lambda Book Report: "Susie Bright's Sexwise", 1996 (Box 18, Folder 315)
    - Black Sheets: "Public Sex: The Culture of Radical Sex", 1996 (Box 18, Folder 316)
    - The Cassell '95-'96 Sexual Politics Catalog: "Nothing But the Girl", 1996 (Box 18, Folder 317)
    - Zizo: "De Pot Met de Pet", July 1996 (Box 18, Folder 318)
    - Girlfriends: "Bookmarks", July-August 1996 (Box 18, Folder 319)
    - Gay Community News: "Nothing But the Girl", July 1996 (Box 18, Folder 320)
    - Bay Area Reporter: "Photographers Phyllis Christopher and Romy Suskin", July 4, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 321)
    - SF Bay Guardian: "Young, Gifted, and Living in the Bay Area", July 1996 (Box 18, Folder 322)
    - Publishers Weekly: "Best American Erotica 1996", August 12, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 323)
    - Time Out: "Muff Stuff", 1996 (Box 18, Folder 324)
    - "Nothing But the Girl" Reviews, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 325)
    - Lambda Book Review: "Nothing But the Girl", August 1996 (Box 18, Folder 326)
    - Pink Paper: "What Lesbians do in Bed and the Great Feminist Divide", 1996 (Box 18, Folder 327)
    - "Bound" Reviews, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 328)
    - Masquerade: "Nothing But the Girl", September-October 1996 (Box 18, Folder 329)
    - Outword: "Nothing But the Girl", September 1996 (Box 18, Folder 330)
    - American Reporter: "No Coffee Table Porn", September 1996 (Box 18, Folder 331)
    - NY Times: "Lesbian Magazines Are Changing, In Quest for Ads", December 23, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - American Bookseller: "Reading on the Edge", October 1996 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Boston Phoenix: "State of Sleaze", October 18, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - PitchWeekly: "'Sexpert' Bright Probes Sexual Ignorance and Porn", November 27-December 4, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - People Online: "Susie Bright online with People Magazine", November 19, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Siegessaule: "Nothing But the Girl", 1996 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Paramour: "Nothing But the Girl", 1996 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - People: "Cyberchats", November 25, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Book Forum: "Nothing But the Girl", November 1996 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Santa Cruz Sentinel: "The Return of Susie Sexpert", November 1996 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - The Harvard Gay and Lesbian Review: "Sexuality is Primarily a Health Issue", 1996 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Village Voice: "Bound and Gagged", September 24, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - The Lesbian Review of Books: "More Chocolate Than You Can Eat", 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Philadelphia City Paper: "Hot Sex", June 9-16, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Examiner: "Susie Bright Porn to be Free", 1996 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Speak: "Susie Bright on Religion, Politics and Everything Else", 1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Intermission: "Erotica Queen", November 7, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Advocate: "Susie Bright Heats Up Bound", November 12, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - NY Observer: "How to Succeed in Sex Without Really Trying", November 21, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Pentimenta: "Lesbian Chic and the Blatant Lesbian Image", 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Penache: "Susie Sexpert: "Soccer Mom", December 1996 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Missoula Independent: "Staff Picks: The Best of '96", January 2-9, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Boston Globe: "Valentine's Day: Hot and Steamy", February 9, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - The Kansas City Star: "Magazine Issue Raises Other Issues", February 12, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Beatrice: Interview, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Jump Cut 41: "Porn-education Roadshows", 1997 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Advocate: "Sexual Crusader", March 4, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - The Valley Advocate: "Sexual Freedom Fighter", March 13-19, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Etc.: "Susie Bright Sexual State", March 14, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Los Angeles Times: "Battle-Ax", March 16, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - The Buffalo News: "Shameless", March 16, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Time Out: "Bright Idease", March 13-20, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - The New York Times: "Beyond Dr. Ruth", March 23, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - The Women's Review of Books: "Chic at a Price", March 1997 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - LA Times: "When All Else Falters, Airbrush", March 27, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Independent: "Liberation Sexology", March 26-April 1, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - City Paper: "Bright-Eyed", March 26-April 2, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Bloot (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Mademoiselle: "What's Sexy?", April 1997 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Out: "Bright Light", April 1997 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Hip Mama: "Susie Bright Talks Parenting, Politics and Porn 101", April 1997 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - San Francisco Chronicle: "Bright, Liberty and the Pursuit of Sexual Happiness", April 2, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Borders appearance, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - The Washington Blade: "Seeking Susie", April 4, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Out and About: "Not For Our Eyes Only", April 3-9, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Village Voice: "Sex and Sensibility", 1997 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Palo Alto Daily News: "Author Gives Palo Alto Crowd a 'Sexual State of the Union'", April 10, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Palo Alto Daily News: "Feminist Author Says Dad Had a Positive Influence", April 14, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - San Jose Mercury News: "Sex and the State", April 20, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - San Francisco Chronicle: "Best Sellers", April 20, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - In These Times: "Ask the Sexpert", April 28, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - New Yorker: "Anti-Climax", April 21, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Lit: "The Last Good Time", May 1, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Lavender: "What's Wrong With America According to Susie Bright", May 9, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - The New Leader: New York Times Book Review "The Seat of Woman's Delight", May 19, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - San Jose Mercury News: "Leading Question Susie Bright", May 25, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Metro Times: "Trying Herself on for Size", May 28-June 3, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Scrawl: "Between the Bright and the Dworkin", 1997 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Utne Reader, May-June 1997 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Bust: "Sexual State of the Union", 1997 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Vanity Fair: "Lover Girls", June 1997 (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Phoenix Literary Section: "Susie Bright on Gay Male Erotica", June 1997 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - San Francisco Weekly: "The House of Tudor", June 11-17, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Cognotes: "Women's Publishing Survival", July 1, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Chicago Tribune: "Bedtime Stories", July 12, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Bookshop Santa Cruz: "Susie Bright's Sexual State of the Union", 1997 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - The "L" word: Sexual State of the Union Reviews", August 1997 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Solidarity Protest: "Sexual Liberation or More of the Same?", August 1997 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - San Francisco Chronicle: "What Does 'Company of Men' Say About Men's Behavior?", August 15, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Metro: "Back to the Garden", August 21-27, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Kirkus Review: "Susie Bright Review", September 1, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Journal Sentinel: "Drive Targets Stores Carrying Books of Nudes", September 10, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Amateur Porn: "Susie Bright's Amateurs", September 15, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - LA Times: "New Wave of Sex Writing", October 13, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Gauntlet: "Sexual State of the Union" review, November 14, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - New Woman: Harriet Lerner's Advice Column, November 1997 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Electronic Newsstand: "On Their Backs, Again", December 1997 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Village Voice: "The Code of Sexual Lying", February 1998 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - Metro Santa Cruz: "Bi By Love", February 11, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Southern Voice: "Bold and Bright", March 12, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Atlanta Journal: "Sexpert Revels in Scandal", March 20, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Encore: "Too Sexy For Your Ears", 1998 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - Curve: "Susie Bright Sexual State of the Union", March 1998 (Box 19, Folder 83)
    - Santa Cruz Sentinel: "Desire's Champion", April 10, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 84)
    - The New Yorker: Book Review, May 11, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 85)
    - Sindication: "Miss Manners", 1998 (Box 19, Folder 86)
    - The Hungry Mind Review: "Is Orgasm a Romantic Moment", 1998 (Box 19, Folder 87)
    - American Journalism Review: "Breaking Through on the Web", June 1998 (Box 19, Folder 88)
    - Williamette: "Rogue of the Week", June 10, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 89)
    - Arizona Daily Star: "Let's Talk About It", June 13, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 90)
    - Paper: "Naked Ambition", July 1998 (Box 19, Folder 91)
    - Bust: "Susie Q's Looking for Mr. Back Door", 1998 (Box 19, Folder 92)
    - New York Post: "XXX-treme New Feminists", July 21, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 93)
    - Lexis-Nexus: TV, radio, and print clippings, August 1996-July 1998 (Box 19, Folder 94)
    - Amica: Viagra reprint from Salon, July 1998 (Box 19, Folder 95)
    - Cupid: "Review of "Nothing But the Girl", 1998 (Box 19, Folder 96)
    - The Playboy Forum: "Knights of the Round Table", September 1998 (Box 19, Folder 97)
    - hip Mama: "Yo Mama's Day Book; Food, Sex, and Relationships", 1998 (Box 19, Folder 98)
    - New York Press: "Best of Manhattan Living", September 23-29, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 99)
    - Daily Sport: "Millions See Lesbo Climax on TV", October 8, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 100)
    - The New York Times Book Review: "What Women Want", November 29, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 101)
    - Zap Comics #14: "Incident at Zwigoff's", November 1998 (Box 19, Folder 102)
    - Wirednews: "Salon May Have to Pull Plug", December 1998 (Box 19, Folder 103)
    - San Francisco Gate: "A Sex-OBsessed Year", December 27, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 104)
    - San Francisco Frontlines: "Tenth Year of Women's Erotic Fiction Collection", December 1998 (Box 19, Folder 105)
    - Kirkus Review: Review of "Best American Erotica 1999", January 15, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 106)
    - Wired: "The Salon Makeover", January 1999 (Box 19, Folder 107)
    - Maximum RocknRoll: "Herotica 10th Anniversary Edition", January 1999 (Box 19, Folder 108)
    - Sonoma County Independent: "Suddenly Susie", February 11-17, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 109)
    - Trade Paperback: "Book Club: Get Sexy", February 1999 (Box 19, Folder 110)
    - San Jose Mercury News: "Dear Moderate Republicans: Good Luck", February 21, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 111)
    - The Boston Phoenix: "Sticky Pages", March 12, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 112)
    - Berkeley Voice: "Still Willing to Take Risks", March 18, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 113)
    - Bust #12: "The Case of the Bashful Bisexual", 1999 (Box 19, Folder 114)
    - The New Yorker: "The Loose Canon", March 29, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 115)
    - Luce Press Clippings: Best American Erotica 1999 review, March 29, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 116)
    - Playboy: "Clit Lit", June 1999 (Box 19, Folder 117)
    - Ms: "The Beauty and the Brains", June-July 1999 (Box 19, Folder 118)
    - The Stranger: The Queer Issue, June 23-29, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 119)
    - Venus or Vixen: Best American Erotica 1999 review, June 1999 (Box 19, Folder 120)
    - Lexis-Nexis: Various Media Pieces, August 23, 1998-July 10, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 121)
    - New York Times: "Batman's Robin Shaves His Legs? Erotica as a Portrait of the Age", July 10, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 122)
    - Publishers Weekly: Full Exposure review, July 12, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 123)
    - Playboy website: Best American Erotica 1999 review, July 1999 (Box 19, Folder 124)
    - Out: "Let the Fur Fly", July 1999 (Box 19, Folder 125)
    - Playboy: "Buzz of the Century", August 1999 (Box 19, Folder 126)
    - San Francisco Chronicle: "The Thing About the Woman Thing", August 2, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 127)
    - Blowfish.com: "Notes from the Buyer", August 30, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 128)
    - Salinas Weekly: "Susie Bright", September 16-22, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 129)
    - Good Times: "Expose Yourself!", September 16, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 130)
    - LA Times: "A Pair of Daring Forays Into Feminine Territory", September 1999 (Box 19, Folder 131)
    - Sonoma County Independent: "Bright Ideas", September 16-22, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 132)
    - Just Out: "Cock Pioneer Hits the Trail to Oregan", September 17, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 133)
    - North Coast Journal: "Bright Ideas About Sex", September 23, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 134)
    - Batteries Not Included: "Reopening Sex World", September 1999 (Box 19, Folder 135)
    - Wired News: "The 'Bright' Side of Sex", September 30, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 136)
    - Seattle Weekly: "Full Frontal Disclosure", September 30, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 137)
    - The Matrix: Full Exposure review, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 138)
    - Utne Reader: "Fully Charged", October 1999 (Box 19, Folder 139)
    - The Boston Phoenix: "Sex with Dan Quayle", October 1999 (Box 19, Folder 140)
    - Luce Press Clippings: "Northern California Best Sellers", October 1999 (Box 19, Folder 141)
    - Mouthorgan.com: "Ten Questions: Susie Bright", October 2, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 142)
    - Joel's Salon: "The Susie Bright 'Beauty' Interview", October 2, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 143)
    - SFSU Student Paper: "Sex Columnists Get Personal", October 7, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 144)
    - hipMama: "Susie Bright: an Interview", October 9, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 145)
    - City Pages: "Susie Bright", October 13, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 146)
    - Metro Times: "Juices Flowing", October 13-19, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 147)
    - Star Tribune: "It's Still all About Sex, Says this Bright Interviewee", October 14, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 148)
    - The Connection: "Susie Bright and the Erotic Life", October 15, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 149)
    - The Stranger: Bestsellers, October 14, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 150)
    - Boston Globe: "Sexplorations at MIT", October 15, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 151)
    - The South End: "Bright Gets Down and Dirty in Sex", October 15, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 152)
    - theStranger.com: "Susie is Bright", October 16, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 153)
    - Between the Lines: "Exploring Erotica", October 21, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 154)
    - Williamette Weekly: "Q and A Susie Bright", October 27, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 155)
    - Comes Naturally: "Full Exposure", October 29, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 156)
    - H and E: "Old and in the Nude", November 1999 (Box 19, Folder 157)
    - Publishers Weekly: "Full Exposure", November 1, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 158)
    - The New York Observer: "Enough! The Overexposure of Sex is Ruining the Mood for Everyone", November 8, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 159)
    - Spectator: "Exposed", November 12-18, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 160)
    - Yahoo: "To Each Her Own", December 1999 (Box 19, Folder 161)
    - Sojourner: "Full Exposure: Bisexual SexGuru Susie Bright Tells All", December 1999 (Box 19, Folder 162)
    - New York Times: "Just Do It", December 12, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 163)
    - The Progressive: "Susie Bright", December 1999 (Box 19, Folder 164)
    - Luce Press Clippings: "That's Life Behind the Labels", December 15, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 165)
    - The Nation: "Blowjobs and Snow Jobs", December 20, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 166)
    - Rainbow Network: "Sexperts: Susie Bright" (Box 19, Folder 167)
    - Amateur Porn: "Bend Over Boyfriend" (Box 19, Folder 168)
    - Playboy Forum: "Bright Ideas", November 1999 (Box 19, Folder 169)
    - Spirit: "Roll Your Own Erotic Manifesto", 2000 (Box 19, Folder 170)
    - Gay and Lesbian Review: "Come Out if You're Gay or Straight", 2000 (Box 19, Folder 171)
    - The Boston Book Review: "Susie Bright: Girl Sloth", January-February 2000 (Box 19, Folder 172)
    - Mixed Media: Full Exposure, January 2000 (Box 19, Folder 173)
    - Publishers Weekly: The Best American Erotica review, January 10, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 174)
    - Lambda Book Report: "Not Your Mother's Damp Panties", January 24, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 175)
    - Third Age.com: "What to Bring on Your Next Fling", February 2000 (Box 19, Folder 176)
    - Clean Sheets: The Best American Erotica 2000 review, February 9, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 177)
    - Washington Post: Best American Erotica 2000 review, February 13, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 178)
    - LA Times: "Venice's Past; The Realist's Future", May 2000 (Box 19, Folder 179)
    - Bust: Susie Q's column #14, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 180)
    - SF Chronicle: "Composer Launches Space Opera", May 19, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 181)
    - SJ Mercury News: "Oh, Susannah!", May 21, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 182)
    - Scottish Daily Record: "Bound" review, June 17, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 183)
    - The Realist: "Susie Bright's Book Tour Diary", 2000 (Box 19, Folder 184)
    - SC Sentinel: "Women Find Meaning in Their Lives During Their 30s", May 26, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 185)
    - Bark: "First Encounters of a Canine Kind", November 12, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 186)
    - Player: Warren Hinckle on Susie, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 187)
    - Bookreporter.com: Susie Bright interview, August 4, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 188)
    - Hip Mama Survival Guide: "Rebel Mom", 2000 (Box 19, Folder 189)
    - Lingua Franca: "Thought Balloons", September 2000 (Box 19, Folder 190)
    - The Industry Standard 'Grok': "Susie Bright", September 2000 (Box 19, Folder 191)
    - The Salt Journal: "Leather and Lace Meet Women's Lib", 2001 (Box 19, Folder 192)
    - The SF Bay Guardian: "Boogie Dykes", January 31-February 6, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 193)
    - The Toronto Star: Best American Erotica 2001 review, February 11, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 194)
    - Playboy: "What 10 Commandments Would You Post in School?", March 2001 (Box 19, Folder 195)
    - Kansas City Star: Best American Erotica 2001 review, March 18, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - On Our Backs: Best American Erotica 2001 review, April-May 2001 (Box 19, Folder 197)
    - Ms.: "Honey, Disney Shrunk the Kids", April-May 2001 (Box 19, Folder 198)
    - Sexual State of the Union at University of Wisconsin-Madison controversy, April 24-May 4, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 199)
    - The Wall Street Journal: "From the Advent of BIrth Control to Bill Clinton's Impeachment: A Look Under the Covers", April 23, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 200)
    - Marie Clarie: "Sex Tips from Easily Orgasmic Women", May 2001 (Box 19, Folder 201)
    - Publishers Weekly: How to Read/Write a Dirty Story review, May 7, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 202)
    - Sydney Morning Herald: "The Nipple Effect", May 12, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 203)
    - Playboy: "Why Johny Can't Screw", June 2001 (Box 19, Folder 204)
    - San Francisco: Special Issue "Life in the Gay Area", June 2001 (Box 19, Folder 205)
    - Article in a Hebrew magazine, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 206)
    - The SF Chronicle: "Stars and Rainbows", June 22, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 207)
    - Chatelaine: "Venus Envy", July 1, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 208)
    - New York Pulse: "Erotica Comes Out of Hiding and Onto the Shelves", July 1, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 209)
    - National Review: "What a Girl Wants", July 9, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 210)
    - Northern California Bohemian: "Robo Job", July 12-18, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 211)
    - Hip Mama: "Exploding the Daddy Myth", 2001 (Box 19, Folder 212)
    - Metro Santa Cruz: "Letters" on Sept. 11 attacks, September 19-26, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 213)
    - The Progressive: "The Orgasm Industry", October 2001 (Box 19, Folder 214)
    - Dwell: "Susie's One Night Stand", October 2001 (Box 19, Folder 215)
    - SF Chronicle: "Face Time", October 7, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 216)
    - The Guardian: "Faith, Hope and Chastity", October 20, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 217)
    - The Village Voice: "Naughty Holiday Gifts", November 30, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 218)